{"data":[{"question":"Television is one of man's important mean of communication.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"is","b":"man's","c":"mean","d":"communication","answer":"3","explain":"- Mean-> means","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"Though TV, home viewers can see and learn about people, places and things in faraway lands.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Though","b":"learn","c":"about","d":"in","answer":"1","explain":"- Though-> through","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"TV provides many more entertainment programs as any other kind.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"many","b":"entertainment","c":"as","d":"any","answer":"3","explain":"- As-> than","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"Poverty desert countries in Africa can grow guayule.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Poverty","b":"countries","c":"in","d":"grow","answer":"1","explain":"- Poverty-> poor","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"The rubber farms will make a lot of money and give jobs to a great deal of people.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"rubber","b":"make","c":"a lot of","d":"a great deal of","answer":"4","explain":"- A great deal of-> many","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"Around the age of sixteen you must make one of the biggest decision of your life.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Around","b":"of","c":"must","d":"decision","answer":"4","explain":"- Decision-> decisions","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"Junko Tabei, is a Japanese from Hokkaido, was the first woman to make this difficult climb.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"is","b":"from","c":"was","d":"to make","answer":"1","explain":"- Is-> was","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"A Tokyo newspaper - television company had organized the climb in 1975.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Tokyo","b":"company","c":"had organized","d":"in","answer":"3","explain":"- Had organized-> had been organized","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"Bill and Fred was students at a university and they were friends.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"and","b":"was","c":"at","d":"were","answer":"2","explain":"- Was-> were","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"The noise on the roof of the trailer woke Bill and Fred up very quick.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"The","b":"of","c":"woke","d":"quick","answer":"4","explain":"- Quick-> quickly","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"}]}